const questionsAndAnswers = [
  {
    question: "Who is best known for their football-shaped head?",
    correct: "Rocko",
    incorrect: ["Arnold", "Dexter", "Goku"]  
  },  
  {
    question: "Who considers themself a 'boy genius' and has their own lab?",
    correct: "Dexter",
    incorrect: ["Sailor Moon", "Chucky", "Doug"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following are made of sugar, spice, and everything nice?",
    correct: "Power Puff Girls",
    incorrect: ["Phil", "Jimmy", "Samurai Jack"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is the name of Scooby Doo's nephew?",
    correct: "Scrappy",
    incorrect: ["Joey", "Snappy", "Slappy"]
  },
  {
    question: "In the Rugrats, who is considered the 'scaredy cat' of the group?",
    correct: "Chuckie",
    incorrect: ["Chunky", "Lil", "Tommy"]
  },
  {
    question: "How many Pokemon were there in the first season of Pokemon?",
    correct: "151",
    incorrect: ["200", "149", "823"]
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of Ash Ketchum's SECOND Pokemon?",
    correct: "Caterpie",
    incorrect: ["Charmander", "Pidgeot", "Mewtwo"]
  },
  {
    question: "In Dragon Ball Z, what is the name of Goku's wife?",
    correct: "Chi-Chi",
    incorrect: ["Bulma", "Videl", "Mr. Popo"]
  },
  {
    question: "Who sacrificed their own life in an attempt to destroy Majin Buu in Dragon Ball Z?",
    correct: "Vegeta",
    incorrect: ["Goku", "Gohan", "Krillin"]
  },
  {
    question: "In the show, Doug, who was Doug's best friend?",
    correct: "Skeeter",
    incorrect: ["Patty Mayonnaise", "Squirt", "Scooter"]
  },
  {
    question: "What color is the tip of Pikachu's tail?",
    correct: "Yellow",
    incorrect: ["Black", "Red", "Blue"]
  },
  {
    question: "In the show, Pokemon, why does Misty initially follow Ash?",
    correct: "To get her bike back",
    incorrect: ["Because she likes him", "He owes her money", "She wants to assassinate him"]
  },
  {
    question: "Complete the following title: 'Courage the cowardly ______?'",
    correct: "Dog",
    incorrect: ["Cat", "Bird", "Pup"]
  },
  {
    question: "In the show 'Hey, Arnold!,' who has a big crush on Arnold?",
    correct: "Helga",
    incorrect: ["Olga", "Phoebe", "Harold"]
  },
  {
    question: "In the show Rocketpower, what is the term used to describe people who wear shoes at the beach?",
    correct: "Shoebies",
    incorrect: ["Tourists", "Shoobs", "Dorks"]
  }
];